ashford.com 2006-06-15

# Ashford.com Helpdesk

Our Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for our website: Ashford.com 

Ashford.com has created this privacy policy to inform you of the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, www.ashford.com. Because Ashford.com wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information (or third party personally identifiable information) of yours is collected from you through our website  

  2. The organization collecting the information  

  3. How the information is used  

  4. With whom the information may be shared  

  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information  

  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Ashford.com's control  

  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that Ashford.com is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact us at 1-866-ASHFORD. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Ashford.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ashford.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**My Account**  
When you make a purchase on our site, you will have the option to create an account. By creating an account, the system will remember your personal and purchase information and the checkout process on future purchases will be fast, easy and always completely secure. At your option, your account can also store important dates such as birthdays or anniversaries and allow you to subscribe to receive promotional emails and announcements from us (see “Electronic Mailings” below).

Creating an account is also fast and easy: simply enter your personal information once and select your very own username and password. Then during checkout on your next purchase, just login and the system will take care of the rest. At all times, your personal information is accessible to you to review, edit, or update as necessary by clicking on the “My Account” link. 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here, is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and shipping information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. 

**Usage Tracking**  
Ashford.com's database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and #of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests. 

**Aggregate Information**  
Ashford.com uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners of Ashford.com to plan advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
Ashford.com gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. Ashford.com will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Ashford.com. 

**Catalog, Newsletters, Etc.**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below. 

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Surveys & Sweepstakes**  
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about an item, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Ashford.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We do store the friend's email and they have an option to opt-out in the communication. 

**Special request page**  
Our customers can use the special request page to enquire about products that they cannot find on the website, such as, for example, special orders. Personal information is gathered during this process. 

**Security**  
Ashford.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information (like your credit card information) online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are fully informed about our security and privacy practices and updated as new policies are added or revised. They are regularly notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website you may contact us at 1-866-ASHFORD. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for ashford.com to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources such as our affiliated websites. For example, in order for Ashford.com to enhance our ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our affiliated sites, Diamond.com, DiamondDepot.com and WorldofWatches.com. When a user makes a purchase from any of these companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences. 

**Special Offers**  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can be done by using the unsubscribe feature in our communication. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

If we decided to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
